Guide to the Francis Francois papers, 1967-2004
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives.
- Series 5: Publications, 1968-2004; (6 boxes)
  - AASHTO Transportation Policy book, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - AASHTOWare Directory, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - AASHTO: What It Is, What It Does, How It Works, 1984-1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Better Transportation, Better Roads, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - The Bottom Line: Transportation Investment Needs, 1998-2002 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Citizen's Ambassador Program Ground Transportation Delegation to the People's Republic of China, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Critical Foundations Protecting America's Infrastructures, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - CWA, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - The Economic Impact of Maryland Highway Investment, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Federal Highway Cost Allocation Study, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Federal Highway Program and Highway Safety: An Economic Analysis, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - FHWA Study for European Intermodal Programs, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Global Intermodal Freight State of Readiness for the 21st Century, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Greater Washington Area Research Center, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Harmonization of Vehicle Weight and Dimension Regulations within the NAFTA Partnership, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Highway Information Quarterly Newsletter, 1999-2002 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Highway Statistics, 1981, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Highway Taxes and Fees, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Innovation Briefs, 1991-2002 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Innovation Briefs, Urban Mobility Corporation, and AASHTO Regs Reports, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Leadership manual, catalog and informational publications, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Maryland Roads, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - News and publications related to AASHTO, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Organizational Charts of AASHTO Member Departments, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Planning for Infrastructure, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - The President's National Urban Policy Report, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Public Works Management and Policy, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - The Road Gang, 1996, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Plan for Environmental Research, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Taking a Stand: Cultivating a New Relationship with the World's Forests, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Transportation for a Competitive America, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Transportation: Driving a Thriving Economy, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Transportation Equity Act for the 21st Century, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Transportation Investment and Economic Expansion: Summary Report, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Transportation in the ISTEA Era, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Transportation Quarterly, 1987, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Transportation Statistics Annual Report, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - TRB Conference/Executive session + press releases, 1995-1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Understanding the Highway Finance Evolution/Revolution, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - US Department of Transportation publications and brochures, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - US DOT guides, newsletters, 1998-1999, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - US DOT ISTEA brochure, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - US DOT publications, other organizational directories/newsletters, 1988, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Various brochures, 1988-1998 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Washington DC Metro, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Series 6: Audiovisual materials and realia, 1988-1997; (2 boxes)
  This series includes items such as an AASHTO calculator and desktop road sign, as well as a CD, VHS tape, and 40 audio cassette tapes from the Transportation Research Board's annual meeting and other organizational meetings. All items in Box 32 are audio cassette tapes except for the order form at the end.
  - AASHTO calculator, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Celebrating America's Highways 40th Anniversary desk billboard, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Transportation Engineers Compendium of Technical Papers from 67th Annual Meeting CD, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Moving Oregon into the 21st Century: A Future Forum VHS, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Moving Beyond Gridlock: Regional Approaches to Manage Traffic and Development, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Moving Beyond Gridlock: Regional Approaches to Manage Traffic and Development, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Preparing for NEXTEA: Lessons Learned from State/MPO Level Freight Data Applications Since ISTEA, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Preparing for NEXTEA: Lessons Learned from State/MPO Level Freight Data Applications Since ISTEA, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - The Evolution of ISTEA: Roles and Responsibilities of Various Levels of Government and the Private Sector, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - The Evolution of ISTEA: Roles and Responsibilities of Various Levels of Government and the Private Sector, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Implementation of the AASHTO LRFD Bridge Specifications, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Implementation of the AASHTO LRFD Bridge Specifications, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - A Look Ahead: Transportation in the 21st Century, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - A Look Ahead: Transportation in the 21st Century, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Management Strategies and Tools for Winter Maintenance Operations, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Management Strategies and Tools for Winter Maintenance Operations, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Traffic Calming, Part 1: Historic Overview and European Case Studies, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Traffic Calming, Part 1: Historic Overview and European Case Studies, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Traffic Calming, Part 3: Major Issues, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Traffic Calming, Part 3: Major Issues, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Rail Mergers: Transportation in the Wake of the BN-SF and UP-SP Mergers, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Rail Mergers: Transportation in the Wake of the BN-SF and UP-SP Mergers, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - University Transportation Centers and Research Institutes: Reauthorize or Not? Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - University Transportation Centers and Research Institutes: Reauthorize or Not? Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Information Needs to Support State and Local Transportation Decision Making into the 21st Century: An Open Forum, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Information Needs to Support State and Local Transportation Decision Making into the 21st Century: An Open Forum, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - International Roundtable, Part 1: Transport Privatization, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - International Roundtable, Part 1: Transport Privatization, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Performance Measures for Transportation, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Performance Measures for Transportation, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Five Years of Intermodalism: What Have We Learned? Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Five Years of Intermodalism: What Have We Learned? Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - ISTEA: Challenges and Opportunities, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - ISTEA: Challenges and Opportunities, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Changing Transportation Organizations, Part 3: Using Measurement Tools and Methods, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Changing Transportation Organizations, Part 3: Using Measurement Tools and Methods, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Full Costing of Transportation Projects, Tape 1, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 76th Annual Meeting - Full Costing of Transportation Projects, Tape 2, January 1997 (Box 32)
  - ATSSA Conference - ISTEA Reauthorization, 1998 (Box 32)
  - ATSSA Conference - Public Officials Forum, 1998 (Box 32)
  - Transportation Research Board - 65th Annual Meeting - Strategic Management: What Works and What Doesn't Work, Tape 2, 1986 (Box 32)
  - American Public Transit Association Meeting, Boston, Mass., October 1982 (Box 32)
  - Chairman's Luncheon, January 15, 1997 (Box 32)
  - AASHTO, July 14 (Box 32)
  - Audio Cassettes Order Form, Transportation Research Board 76th Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 32)